

# Ali Göktuğ Yalçın

**Date of birth:** 04/05/1998

**Gender:** Male

**Nationality:** Turkish

## **CONTACT**

- Mahmut Şevket Paşa Caddesi, Ridaniye Sokak, No:12, Daire:
   Çeliktepe/Kağıthane/ İstanbul, null
   34732 İstanbul, Turkey
- 🔽 goktugyalcin06@gmail.com
- (+90) 5417327426
- https://github.com/
  GoktugYalcin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/
yalcing/

#### SKILLS

# Info

I started development with console apps on C/C++. On first 2 years of the branch, I interested in hardware like Real-Time Systems and simple, daily IoT projects. Developed many projects with NFC and Bluetooth Communication.

Last 2 years, I'm very interested in Mobile and Web Development with JavaScript and it's frameworks. Developed projects mostly Pure JS or React.js, many projects on Vue.js and Angular.js.

Also, I used Python Frameworks for little projects and scripts.

Nowadays, I focused on improve my skills on React, Vue and Svelte as a Frontend Developer

<u>GitHub</u> LinkedIn

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**02/07/2018 - 10/08/2018** - İstanbul, Turkey

#### Intern

Selçuk Ecza Deposu A.Ş.

In this term, I worked with network systems of the company. With this, I learned Cisco IP Systems, I could describe and solve any problem, when it appears about Cisco.

Also I learn management of the multiply systems, what includes the offices.

Information and communication

**19/08/2019 - 20/09/2019** - Sakarya, Turkey

#### Intern

Virtual Reality Lab, Sakarya University

Term was based on develop projects on microcontrollers like Raspberry Pi and Arduino.

We developed a Plate Recognize Based Parking Lot System with Python&OpenCV2.

Also I learned Socket Messaging with C/C++.

Information and communication

02/2021 - 08/2021 - Istanbul, Turkey

## Javascript Developer

Netuce

Worked as a Full Stack Dev. Developed CRM app on EcmaScript6 and CSS. Also I used MySQL and many Profiling frameworks.

08/2021 - CURRENT - Istanbul, Turkey

Frontend Developer

Next4biz

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

09/2016 - 08/2021

**Computer Engineering** 

Sakarya University

sakarya.edu.tr

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Türkçe

**OTHER LANGUAGE(S):** 

İngilizce

<b>Listening</b> B2	<b>Reading</b> C2	Spoken production C1	Spoken interaction C1	<b>Writing</b> C1
Fransızca Listening A1	<b>Reading</b> A1	Spoken production A1	Spoken interaction A1	<b>Writing</b> A1

#### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

## **Mobile Development**

React Native / Nativescript / Reactjs

**Web Development** 

CSS SASS SCSS / Django / RESTful API / JavaScript

**General Purpose** 

C / C++ / Git / Python

**Database and Data Storage** 

MongoDB / Google Firebase / SQLite

Hardware

Raspberry Pi / Microprocessors / Arduino

#### **DRIVING LICENCE**



**Driving Licence:** B